(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-04T22:28:31.412011",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
Ow!
Huh
Come chase me
Every day I spent crying 'bout
almost-loves turned complicated
On the way, yeah
My heart got torn up, shredded, all but dead, and
Now they say I, I'm just a masochist
They're sick of it, boy, take a hint
You ain't gon' ever get this
Pedal to the metal
Shooting straight to the stars
Got a craving like the danger on me
Yeah, she like it like that, like that
Up another level
Temptation you just can't deny
Come get a taste, but can't say I won't bite
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna...
Ah...
In my eyes, Nirvana
Oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta...
Run
But it's fun to see you try
So hit me up!
Off the map I'mma take it, all my energy
Speeding up fast, ready, target locked
So hit me up!
Hit the dash, I'm upgraded and you want a piece
So hit me up, ah, I never stop
In a new territory
I'm on the edge of glory
Boy, just watch how I move
Gimme that rush
Got no regrets in my mind
Boy, it's on you this time, so hit me up
Outta luck, volume up, you got a crush?
Such a cliché, your bad boy charms
Thought I'd fall right back in your arms
Wasn't enough, you needed more
Now you're begging to let you score
Surely you'll take it all in stride
I'mma be busy tonight
Goodbye, goodbye, gotta leave you dry
Always try'na play it cool
20/20 vision on me
Just outside my field of view
Yeah, she like it like that, like that
Engine booming, that's my cue
Catch me if you can, you better
Keep up the chase, boy, you're falling behind
Supersonic, I'm heading out, I'm gonna...
Ah...
In my eyes, Nirvana
Oh, I'm taking off now!
Pushing for the high, my lover, I gotta...
Spun to see you try...
So hit me up!
Off the map, I'm gonna take it all, my energy
Speeding up fast, ready, target locked!
So hit me up!
Head-to-dash, I'm upgraded and you wanna be...
So hit me up, ah, and never stop!
In a new territory, I'm on the edge of glory
Give me that rush!
Got no regrets in my mind, point to a new design, so hit me up, turn the light volume up!
You got a crush!
Ah, just barely wasn't enough, you should've
Ah, given me all that you got, you could've
Coming full circle, I got the nerve, oh!
Top spot getting hot, watch me run it up!
So hit me up!
Rev it up and make that vroom vroom vroom vroom!
When I hit you with that zoom zoom zoom zoom!
So hit me up!
If you know what's good for you, ooh ooh ooh
Feel me now, I'm back in charge right now, off the dial!
Yay! Kick-off!
Welcome to my Birthday in 2025!
お誕生日です！私の、なんと、なんと！何歳になってるんでしょう、この不死鳥？
It's my birthday! I'm... wait, wait! How old is this Phoenix getting, I wonder?
It is my birthday! It is a very special occasion!
It is not just my birthday, it is also the Super Special Summer!
We will make it a super special summer today, yes, yes!
And if you guys want, I have a hashtag up here, so please make use of it! It is #KiaraBDay2025!
So post it all over social media!
Screenshots, or GIFs or JIFs, whatever you want, share it to the world, spread the KFP love!
Thank you already in advance!
We started the first song with KIDAS's "HIT ME UP".
KIDAS... another banger from my good friend KIDAS!
Thank you for providing the world with bangas! I'm taking them for myself, ehehe, they're mine now!
Yeah, that was fun! And did you like the little spicy dance? Hehehe!
And let's take a little look at the stage! ステージも見ましょうか？
And let's take a little look at the stage! Shall we look at the stage too?
Well, besides the Super Special Summer logo, we have some presents! I wonder what's inside?
And some balloons, maybe I'm gonna pop them when I'm done here, ehehe!
Yes! And then, besides that...
Today, you know why it's... why it's so special?
Well, because we're gonna have super special merch at the end, we're gonna have...
super special outside guest! Ah! I never had an outside guest before! Exciting!
And, and, and... super special song reveal? Hm! Yeah, yeah, probably. You know me!
So please watch until the very end! 最後まで見届けてください！
So please watch until the very end! Please watch until the very end!
特別なサプライズいっぱいありますから！よろしくお願いします！
There are lots of special surprises, so please look forward to it!
Please listen to the next song: UNDEAD!
Unhappy? If you're dealing with a lotta woes
Unlucky? Then you got to listen very close
Be happy! Keep on trying, never give up
Don't forget that you're alive
The past you have been running from
That boring future yet to come
Still counseling you
Oh my, oh my
Universal peace peace yeah
Unhappy?
Unlucky?
Be happy!
Undead, oh
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Somehow feeling like there's a fight within and it's been going on so long
I don't feel it and don't even wanna try
Past version of me, of me, of me
And those figures of the old
Transparent ghosts over my route
The childish and painful memories have the deepest roots
Saddening?
Nowhere to be seen
Say what?
Way better then? Irony
They all see the me of the past when looking at me now
Nonsense
Label I can't erase
Yes!
In essence, a complex
It's almost like something's possessing me
It is wrapping tight around
And won't loosen its bounds
The self I used to be before
Undead, oh
Still alive
Time is a chain of your own path
To be alive is to always embrace your inner changes, on and on
Don't settle for unhappiness
Don't be complacent in distress
Not even trying to seize the joy and be happy, you coward
Oh, this world, oh, this world is one odd, one odd fantasy
Who knows what is coming up next, a monster or a snake?
This is a story starting after that encounter, finally
With people or monsters and spirits
Back on topic
Peace, peace yeah
Past & future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
Cutting in
Somehow feeling like there's nothing to be looking forward to
...thrill is what I really want now
And this is the way that guidance grew
Rising compliance, too
It's like I'm going under a lid
I consumed everything
This one or that one or whichever, and now it all just tastes the same
Undead
Still alive, time is a chain of your own path
In any era, your past and your future are in this very moment
Fulfill the life you're set upon
And truthfully keep moving on
Go for that happy ending
Undead
Still alive, I'm telling this to you, now
So never give up on pursuing your happiness and keep being human
'Cause being numb to suffering, always enduring everything
It's almost as if you're dead
A lot of corpses undead, oh
Unhappy? If you're dealing with a lotta woes
Unlucky? Then you gotta listen very close
Be happy! Keep on trying, never give up
Undead, oh, be aware that you're alive
Drowning deep in unhappiness
Or seizing that true happiness
It's on you, on you, it's all on you
Universal, all embracing, all creations
Universal, all-embracing all creations,
Peace, peace, yeah
Past & future
Can't change the past
Run for the future
Where people gather and go
You'll find all worries and woes
Oh, you gotta live on, through this tale of
Monsters everywhere that you can see
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！ Rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān! Rise up Pikkān!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！ Rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān! Rise up Pikkān!
一緒になって輝け Ready 3, 2, 1, Ah!
Shine bright together! Ready, 3, 2, 1, ah!
サドイカ Summer, all in my head, let's go!
Sad or darkest summer, all in my head, let's go!
もう逃げそう 無理そう とかそんな答え Let's go!
Feels like running away, seems impossible, no such answer, let me go!
やっちゃい BIG UP! 勝っちゃい BIG UP! PASSION ばれ！
Do it, big up! Win it, big up! Expose that passion!
失敗じゃない 最低もない 最果てまで追いかけてけ！
It's not a failure, not the worst, chase it to the ends!
隠された想いが 愛 愛 僕らを強くする
Our hidden feelings, love, love, make us stronger.
出会いとはこれ 重なる支えを
This is an encounter; with overlapping support,
言葉つくっていこう
let's create words and keep going!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！ Rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān! Rise up Pikkān!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！ Rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān! Rise up Pikkān!
一緒になって輝け Ready 3, 2, 1, Ah!
Shine bright together! Ready, 3, 2, 1, ah!
YEAH! 最高だぜ この上ない NON-STOP PARTY
Yeah! It's the best, an unparalleled non-stop party!
あっという間に上がれる限界 YEAH!
In the blink of an eye, we soar past our limits, yeah!
何回だだってたって晴れ 傘なんていらないや 雨
No matter how many times, it clears up; no need for an umbrella in the rain!
ワイワイ Don't you dare つかむかい やってやろうぜ
Cheering wildly, don't you dare! Are you ready to grab it? Let me do this!
MAYDAY 助け合えば問題ないね
Mayday! If we help each other, there's no problem!
絶望に見る希望 明日も君と旅するでしょう 約束がちゃんと待ってるんだ OK
Finding hope in despair, we'll surely journey together again tomorrow; our promise is waiting for us, OK!
悲しみから抜くドア 愛 愛
The door that escapes from sadness, love, love,
もうやめ 弱くない
stop it now, we are not weak!
乗り越え咲かせる 負けない強さ
Overcoming it to bloom, an unyielding strength,
言葉つくっていこう
let's create words and keep going!
RISE UP! 描く抜群なステキ願い
Rise up! Picturing our outstanding, wonderful wishes,
RISE UP! 描く可能性の間違い
Rise up! Drawing mistakes among possibilities,
未来つないで 叶え 3, 2, READY, BIG BANG!
connecting the future, making it real, 3, 2, ready, Big Bang!
あがれ 僕らのための冒険だ GO GO! LET'S GO!
Rise up, this is an adventure for us! Go go! Let's go!
ハンパじゃない 燃えてる想いは上昇中
It's no joke, these burning feelings are soaring!
生まれる感傷は 君の消しゴムで消してほしい
I want you to erase these emerging emotions with your eraser.
期待は好きなだけ 全部僕らのため
As many expectations as you like, all for our sake!
RISE UP! 描く抜群なステキ願い
Rise up! Picturing our outstanding, wonderful wishes,
RISE UP! 描く可能性の間違い
Rise up! Drawing mistakes among possibilities,
未来つないで 叶え 3, 2, READY, BIG BANG!
connecting the future, making it real, 3, 2, ready, Big Bang!
あがれ 僕らのための冒険だ GO GO! LET'S GO!
Rise up, this is an adventure for us! Go go! Let's go!
Yeah! Woo! 火テル JOURNEY その向こうに HOT STEP GET UP!
Yeah! Woo! A fiery journey, beyond that, hot step, get up!
COME ON RISE UP! 改訂していこう 予想できそうさ
Come on, rise up! Let's revise as we go, it seems predictable!
Oh, rise up ピッカーン！ Rise up ピッカーン！
Oh, rise up Pikkān! Rise up Pikkān!
Okay, okay, okay, let's do...
Okay, okay, okay, let me do...
self-introductions, even though they don't really need one.
Let's start with the senpai.
イェーイ！ はろー！ 5期生の桃鈴ねねー！
Yay! Hello! 5th Generation, Momosuzu Nene!
5期生じゃなかったっけ？
Wasn't it 5th generation?
5期生！ 5期生ジェネレーション！
5th Generation! 5th Generation!
と、後輩！
And the kohai!
はろー！ holoX、風真いろはでござる！
Hello! holoX's Kazama Iroha de gozaru!
あんまり英語入ってなかった気がする。
I feel like there wasn't much English in there.
あ、そう...
Ah, right...
There was no English!
English so difficult! Sorry 海外ニキ！
English so difficult! Sorry, overseas fans!
Okay, ねねち！
Okay, Nenechi!
It's been a while! 久しぶりだね！
It's been a while! It's been a while, hasn't it?
It's been a while! It's been a while! Wow!
Two years maybe? Maybe two years?
That we danced together.
since we danced together?
Long time ago? 寂しかったよ！
Long time ago? I missed you!
Long time... Last year!
Ah, last year! Last year, yeah!
Yeah! I'm happy, happy! Happy, happy!
I feel like our colors match very well, right?
So maybe if Nenechi is in the middle...
Look! Gradation!
Blonde, peach, orange!
Yellow! Beautiful! Beautiful! 目の色も！
Yellow! Beautiful! Beautiful! Eye colors too!
いろはちゃん... あ、確かに！ Eye color in my hair!
Iroha-chan... Ah, that's true! Eye color in my hair!
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes! Beautiful!
シナジーを感じる！ ということで...
I feel the synergy! So...
The song we just sang together...
We cannot say too clearly what it was all about,
but did you see this pose here?
What is this pose? I wonder...
We're holding some kind of ball here.
But it could also very well be baseball?
野球？ 野球かな？ 野球！
Baseball? Baseball maybe? Baseball!
と言ったことで！
So with that said!
I want everybody to show me an original throwing pose, okay?
Challenge! 行け、行け！
Challenge! Go, go!
Yes, yes! かっこいい、かわいい、何でもOK！
Yes, yes! Cool, cute, anything is OK!
I start, okay? I start!
Here we go! Ball throwing challenge!
Three, two, one, ホイ！ ホイ！
Three, two, one, hoi! Hoi!
かっこいい！ セクシー！
Cool! Sexy!
セクシー！ かっこいい！ セクシー！
Sexy! Cool! Sexy!
Okay, okay! Next! 誰、誰不満持つ？
Okay, okay! Next! Who's up next?
ねね！ ねね！ ねね！ 見る、見る、見る！
Nene! Nene! Nene! Let me see, let me see!
Let's go! 行け、行け！
Let's go! Go, go!
飛んだ！
She jumped!
ホイ！ ボール！ イボイボボール！
Hoi! Ball! Spiky ball!
ボールイボイボボール？ あ、ボウリング？
Spiky ball? Ah, bowling?
Okay, okay! Cute! Very cute!
いろはちゃん！ 今年度もそういうの欲しいな。
Iroha-chan! I want something like that from you too!
なんかクールなことやって、なんか。
Do something cool or something.
行きますよ！ 来てくれるかな？
Here I go! Will it work?
パッ！ からの、斬撃！
Pah! And then, a slash!
斬！ 斬！ ナイス斬撃！ 斬撃！
Slash! Slash! Nice slashes! Slashes!
またつまらぬものを斬ってしまったでござる。
Once again, I have cut a worthless object.
Very nice! Very nice!
The viewers in the audience maybe can tell us which one was best.
But for now, because I still have many more guests and many more songs...
I have to take this jacket off. So please...
着替え！ 着替え！ 隠さなきゃ！ 隠せ、隠せ！
Changing! Changing! We gotta hide her! Hide her, hide her!
見ないで、見ないで！
Don't look, don't look!
じゃーん！ かわいい！
Ta-da! So cute!
Thank you, thank you! かわいい！
Thank you, thank you! So cute!
So we already have to say goodbye. もうバイバイの時間ですね。
So we already have to say goodbye. It's already time to say goodbye.
でもありがとう！ Thank you! 楽しかった！
But thank you! Thank you! It was so much fun!
またやりましょう！ 次の曲も頑張ってね！
Let me do it again! Do your best on the next song too!
頑張ってください！ バイバイ！
Do your best! Bye-bye!
Can I get it, get it, get all your attention?
Can I get all your attention?
I bet you don't know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
Piercing deep into your core with my gaze,
溢れる様 IQ ammo
overflow like IQ ammo.
獲る天下
Taking over the world,
A catalyst, I know
When I say go, put your hands up
混沌の最中に 降臨した女神
A goddess descended into the midst of chaos,
I freeze it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know but you don't
震撼させる異脳
an extraordinary mind that shakes everything.
I'mma go, I'mma shine, shine, shine, shine
I'm gonna go, I'm gonna shine, shine, shine, shine
Can't stop 煌めく my fantasy
Can't stop my sparkling fantasy
Now you see
星空を濃く染めるんだ 黄昏に
Dyeing the starry sky deeply in the twilight...
Heading to where in my universe, come find me now
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の新髄を見せてあげるから Baby for now
I'll show you the essence of a world yet unseen, baby for now...
Calm down, let me focus. Under my spell like hypnosis. So don't get too close when I...
Come-come-coming through, you wanna roll with me
Come-come-coming through, we're taking down, yeah
I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove. Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do, know that I'm bulletproof. Cold when I do what I do, when I focus.
Hold me back at my best, I finesse what does no one know, 潜む勝負の secret
Hold me back at my best, I finesse what no one knows, a hidden secret match...
Listening cool, my attitude, target in my sight, lock in, ready to shoot, right?
Mayday, this is an emergency! Working under pressure, baby, I can do this in my sleep!
世の理だって覆してしまうような夏の
A summer that could even overturn the rules of the world...
When I go, when I go, I'm a shine, shine, shine, shine
When I go, when I go, I'm gonna shine, shine, shine, shine
Won't stop, I'mma make my fantasy
Now you see
銀河を 音調は外の熱唱に
The galaxy, its melody blending into the passionate singing outside...
Heading to where in my universe, come find me now
Clear my mind of all this doubt
まだ見ぬ世界の新髄をこの目で体感したいから Baby for now
I want to experience the essence of an unseen world with my own eyes, baby for now...
Calm down, let me focus. Under my spell like hypnosis. So don't get too close when I...
Come-come-coming through, you wanna roll with me
Come-come-coming through, we're taking down, yeah
I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove. Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do, know that I'm bulletproof. Cold when I do what I do, when I focus.
Oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh
立てる音 Don't break my focus
The noises around... Don't break my focus!
Oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma
Wanna try and play catch up, follow my mind
I'm gonna get 'em talking about it loud, can't get rid of me now
You and soon to be disowned, put my feet on the ground
任せとくわ A piece of cake, it's no stress
Leave it to me, a piece of cake, it's no stress!
今中魅了して What's next? Take a guess, yes!
Captivating everyone now, what's next? Take a guess, yes!
I tell you what to do, I got nothing to prove. Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus.
I tell you what to do, know that I'm bulletproof. Cold when I do what I do, when I focus.
Oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh
立てる音 Don't break my focus
The noises around... Don't break my focus!
Oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma, oh-ma
Wanna try and play catch up, follow my mind
Focus
とべ、起こせ！ 願うは事故
Fly, get moving! All I want is trouble!
一世一代 さあ何賭す？
Once in a lifetime opportunity, so what will you bet?
自問自答 勝つか負けるか ドローなんてないわ
Asking myself, victory or defeat? There's no such thing as a draw
幕開けるわ
Let's open the curtains
カッチンして ラッキーマネー どっちも無理ー…
Clinking coins, lucky money, both are impossible...
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
Can you draw or not? It's all up to yourself
余裕で！ 振り切り 全betだぜい イェイ☆
Piece of cake! Going all out, I'm betting it all, yay☆!
そこどけ！ そうこのエース かっさらうのはアタシだ
Out of the way! I'm the one taking this ace
Stay もういい 勝ったなら平常心ね プレイボーイ 行け Don't get in my way じゃあね 黙って
Stay, I've had enough! If I win, I'll stay calm. Playboy, beat it! Don't get in my way, bye, shut up!
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー Sit down, sit down
One, two, three! One, two, three! One, two, three! Sit down, sit down!
はーもうフリーズ キメてや 投げるのは賽？才？か匙か？
Ah, frozen now! Decide, what are you throwing? Dice? Talent? Or giving up?
そんな小さい尺度じゃ計れないでしょう♪ そうでしょう♪
You can't measure with such a small ruler, right? Isn't that right?
セイ・グッド・バイや あっちこっちそっちどっち？ Nothing, nothing
Say goodbye! Over there, here, where is it? Nothing, nothing!
病む 道なき道より 闇々嫌
Sick of it, worse than a pathless road, hating the dark
空回りしそう でもまだ止めないで
Feels like spinning in circles, but don't stop yet...
あーのまれそう 声々、それぞれに
Ah, about to be swallowed by all these voices...
Get one's way!
アンタはここまで 後ろだけ見とけ
That's it for you! Just watch from behind
カッチンして ラッキーマネー どっちも無理ー…
Clinking coins, lucky money, both are impossible...
引けるか否か 自分次第だな
Can you draw or not? It's all up to yourself
余裕で！ 振り切り 全betだぜい イェイ☆
Piece of cake! Going all out, I'm betting it all, yay☆!
そこどけ！ そうこのエース かっさらうのはアタシだ
Out of the way! I'm the one taking this ace
Stay もういい 勝ったなら平常心ね プレイボーイ 行け Don't get in my way じゃあね 黙って
Stay, I've had enough! If I win, I'll stay calm. Playboy, beat it! Don't get in my way, bye, shut up!
え、だって
Wait, but...
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three
sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three
まさかの倍々
Unbelievable double double $
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three
sit down, sit down
ワンツースリー ワンツースリー ワンツースリー
One, two, three, one, two, three, one, two, three
sit down, sit down
I like it, like it, ah! I like it, like it! I like it, like it, ah!
I like him tall, he's my 完全形な究極体 必要なんの？ ただ numbers and code, uh-uh
I like him tall, he's my perfect, ultimate form. What do I need? Just numbers and code, uh-uh.
あまくクリエイト 否定的な騒々しい
Sweetly create, negative and noisy.
いく？ 誰でも Click! Make it, make it, snap that!
Ready? Anyone can click! Make it, make it, snap that!
教えてあげるよ
I'll show you.
イニシエ Trick
Initiate trick.
一線を超えると 天国 もう倍狂
Crossing the line into heaven, going twice as crazy.
Make it, make it, snap that!
Oh my lie 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh my lie, even if I'm exhausted, I don't wanna believe it.
018 僕のためだけ toy 愛される
018, a toy just for me, loved.
かぐや あま あま や あま
Kaguya, sweet, sweet, oh sweet.
Puzzle pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love, fitting perfectly right now.
Fake Heart, Fake Heart
Puzzle pieces of love もっと 僕の幸せに
Puzzle pieces of love, even more for my happiness,
Style up and complete
Fake, fake, Fake Heart!
Fake, fake でバラバラ
Scattered with fakes.
何度も Restarting Fake Heart is my target
Restarting time and time again, Fake Heart is my target.
What's the matter? What's the matter?
やり合い世界 変えていきましょう
Let's change this world of conflict.
くっきりくっきり 誰でも神に Yeah
Clear and distinct, anyone can become a god, yeah.
リセットする感覚 Boom boom boom
A sense of resetting, boom boom boom.
ここが僕の Playground 未来の展示開催
This is my playground, an exhibition of the future.
100%満足 約束しますから
I promise 100% satisfaction.
行ったきりとか時代遅れ ついて来さもなくば
Talking about having been there is so outdated, keep up or else.
No love
執着した君の
Of your obsessed...
Oh my lie 疲れ果てても信じたくない
Oh my lie, even if I'm exhausted, I don't wanna believe it.
018 僕のためだけ toy 愛される
018, a toy just for me, loved.
かぐや あま あま や あま
Kaguya, sweet, sweet, oh sweet.
Puzzle pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love, fitting perfectly right now.
Fake Heart, Fake Heart
Puzzle pieces of love もっと 僕の幸せに
Puzzle pieces of love, even more for my happiness,
Style up and complete
Fake, fake, Fake Heart!
Fake, fake でバラバラ
Scattered with fakes.
何回も Restarting Fake Heart is my target
Restarting time and time again, Fake Heart is my target.
夢か 現実か どちらでもいい
Dream or reality, either is fine.
一緒に行きたい Oh yeah
I want to go with you, oh yeah.
虚構のフレームに プログラム プログラム
In a frame of fiction, program, program.
実現まで急ぐの 命は短し
Hurry until it comes true, life is short.
Perfect!
Again!
何が悪いわけ？
What's wrong with that?
Puzzle pieces of love 今 完璧にフィットする
Puzzle pieces of love, fitting perfectly right now.
Fake Heart, Fake Heart
Puzzle pieces of love もっと 僕の幸せに
Puzzle pieces of love, even more for my happiness,
Style up and complete
Para para like it, like it!
劇的人生は Fiction
Dramatic life is fiction.
Para para like it, like it!
難易度 宇宙級の
Cosmic-level difficulty...
Para para like it, like it!
今からもう最高
Awesome from now on.
Para para like it, like it!
楽しんで
Have fun!
Oh...
my heart starts skipping a beat
紐解いた新章
Unraveling a new chapter
様変わりしてゆく show time
A transforming show time
全然悪くない イマジネーション
Not bad at all, imagination
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in my vision clears away
悲しみに別れを告げる
Saying goodbye to sadness
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Tossing both the bitter and sweet into the air
バラインクはバラ色
Rose ink is rose-colored,
どれだけ上手く見せようとしても
no matter how well I try to put on a show.
君がいなければ 何の意味もない
If you're not here, it means nothing at all.
擦り傷すらつかない幻想
An illusion that doesn't leave even a scratch,
針の落ちないレコードさ
a record where the needle never drops.
たった今 ためらいのない 追い風にして
Making this hesitation-free tailwind right now...
吹き荒れる向かい風にも怯まず
Undaunted by the raging headwind,
なびかせて
letting it sway in the breeze.
飛び乗って To the future
Jump aboard, to the future!
ライン引いたって All right, Restart line
Even if a line is drawn, all right, restart line!
腹決めてしまえば
Once you make up your mind,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye.
ひとつひとつすべてが drama
Every single thing is a drama,
待ちわびた day, Restart line
the long-awaited day, restart line!
目変わる パノラマ
A changing panorama,
満ちあふれる Feeling gradation
an overflowing feeling gradation.
始まりのその時が来た
The time for the beginning has come.
Nothing is impossible
まやかししか聞かない世界
A world that listens only to deceptions.
この先はまだ誰も知らない世界
Beyond here is a world nobody knows yet.
傍観してるだけじゃ味気ない
Just being a bystander is dull,
リアルタイムで通じ合って
connecting in real time.
振り切りにかけるモーション
Motion betting on breaking through,
あと論理的にも I don't mind
logically speaking too, I don't mind.
劇的 シチュエーション
A dramatic situation,
いけるどこまでいってみたい
I want to see how far I can go.
選択肢にない Get off the way
Not an option, get off the way!
数多を貫くような真っ直ぐな痛みが
A straightforward pain that pierces through...
どうなっても
No matter what happens,
この手をつないで果てまで
holding hands until the very end,
Keep running to the end
飛び乗って To the future
Jump aboard, to the future!
ライン引いたって All right, Restart line
Even if a line is drawn, all right, restart line!
腹決めてしまえば
Once you make up your mind,
瞬く間に広がる解放区
an open zone spreads in the blink of an eye.
ひとつひとつすべてが drama
Every single thing is a drama,
待ちわびた day, Restart line
the long-awaited day, restart line!
目変わる パノラマ
A changing panorama,
満ちあふれる Feeling gradation
an overflowing feeling gradation.
飛び出せ You make me up
Leap forward, you make me up!
恐れるものはない Restart line
There's nothing to fear, restart line!
綺麗な朝焼けが 透明な明日を照らすよ
A beautiful morning glow illuminates a clear tomorrow.
Restart line!
キアラ先輩！ハッピーバースデー！
Kiara-senpai! Happy birthday!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you! Well, you wished me happy birthday,
but since we went to Austria together, can you say it in German?
Sure! Sure!
Okay, I'll teach you! You don't know, right? Sorry!
教えてくれるんだ、よかった！
Oh, you're going to teach us? That's great!
It's "Alles Gute"! "Alles Gute"! "Gute"?
"Gute"? "Alles Gute zum Geburtstag"! "Geburtstag"!
Oh! Okay! Okay!
せーの！ Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!
Ready, set! Alles Gute zum Geburtstag!
ありがとう！もはやオーストリア人！やったー！
Thank you! You're basically native Austrians now! Yay!
Thank you! ツッコミだけ？まだやってる？
Thank you! Just tsukkomi? Are you still doing it?
Okay, 自己紹介 in English!
Okay, self-introductions in English!
誰から？リリカ！
Who's first? Ririka!
はい！ Hello, everyone! Cute, positive energy, genius! I'm Ririka Ichijou from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Nice to meet you!
Yes! Hello, everyone! Cute, positive energy, genius! I'm Ririka Ichijou from Hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS! Nice to meet you!
はい！儒烏風亭らでん from ホロライブDEV_IS ReGLOSS!
Yes! Juufuutei Raden from hololive DEV_IS ReGLOSS!
イエーイ！ぺらぺら～！
Yay! Pera pera~!
Okay, everyone! We danced your song together!
Yay! Thank you! Thank you! I'm so happy! Feeling ぐらでーしょんです！
Yay! Thank you! Thank you! I'm so happy! Feeling Gradation!
I felt... I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song cause it's so cool! めっちゃかっこいい曲！
I felt... I'm feeling very happy to be able to dance this song cause it's so cool! It's such a cool song!
How was it to dance with like a non-ReGLOSS member?
How was it to dance with a non-ReGLOSS member?
It's actually our first time to dance together with who is not ReGLOSS members, so...
It's actually our first time to dance together with someone who isn't a ReGLOSS member, so...
I was a little bit nervous, but... we can do it! Yay! Happy!
I think, you know, I chose the white version of this outfit because I thought we look so good together!
So, because we look so good together, let's take a cute picture, okay?
Strike a pose! I will go like here.
Closer, closer, closer, closer! Okay!
Yay! 画面ショット！画面ショット！
Yay! Screenshot! Screenshot!
Okay! Thank you, thank you! I had so much fun!
We too! 楽しかった！スパ竹！
Us too! It was so much fun! Super Dake!
じゃあ、えー、『Feeling Gradation』を、ReGLOSSのこの可愛いお二人と一緒に踊りましたけども...
Well then, we just danced "Feeling Gradation" with these two cute ReGLOSS members...
I have even more guests coming, and even more songs coming! And for that, I will go to the center stage!
またねー！バイバイ！スパ竹！がんばれー！
See you! Bye-bye! Super Dake! Good luck!
帰ろー！ランダランダ...
Let's go home! Randa randa...
出会え 出会え 刻む街角で 祝え 宴 歌え 大胆な幕開け
Gather, gather at the street corner, celebrate, feast, sing, a bold curtain-raiser!
つまらない くだらない ならば Dance, dance, dance ありきたりな毎日 ちょっと抜け出し
Boring and pointless? Then dance, dance, dance! Break away from ordinary days!
欲しがってるのは最新型の感情 そんでもって無限永久の情緒
What I crave is state-of-the-art emotion, along with infinite, eternal sentiment!
焦燥だってちょっとじゃん？ 今を射抜いて行く
Impatience is just a little thing, right? Piercing through the present!
愛してバースデイ 祝わんかい ときめきにネバーギブアップ 連れ出して 連れ出して その歌で
Love me, it's my birthday, celebrate it! Never give up on the excitement! Take me away with that song!
そんな僕らが出会えば 特別 映えるワンシーン 目移りない夜へ
When we meet like this, it becomes a special, picture-perfect scene, heading into an unfaltering night!
ほどけたシューレース 結び直して 道なき道へ Roll back, new, new way
Retying my untied shoelaces, off to pathless roads, roll back, new, new way!
成るようになれで幾度目かの後悔中 失敗談も自己流のオルタナティブ
Regretting for the nth time after letting things be, even failures are my own alternative!
欠けてるどこかがルーツなの
The missing pieces are my true roots!
泣いて泣いて涙を伸ばしたら その分だけ星になれ キラめいて
If you cry and wipe away your tears, become a star that sparkles just as much!
不安で手先が震えてっちゃう あの日の輝く目撃が今だ解けない
My hands tremble with anxiety, that dazzling sight from that day still hasn't faded!
引き解けた夢の踊り場 与えられる答えなんかきっと
On the landing of unraveling dreams, any answer given to us is surely...
勝手気ままに 懲り懲りさ 時代のノア リバー 出し抜く運命は正解
Selfish and arbitrary, I'm sick of it! A Noah's river of the era, outsmarting fate is the right answer!
揺らぐ心に沈みつけ
Sinking into a swaying heart...
どうせ僕たちは ネバーギブアップ 踊らせて 踊らせて その歌で
Anyway, we will never give up! Make us dance, make us dance to that song!
アンサーを選んで見つけた また咲き色めく世界 愛してバースデイ
Choosing and finding the answer, a world blooming in vivid colors again, love me, birthday!
絡みつくこの響きは変わらずに
This intertwining resonance remains unchanged!
合図はここから 君に通知 愛しているよ ずっと果たすべき僕で
The signal starts here, notifying you! I love you, as the me who must always fulfill my promise!
白に白重ねて 散らすな 色に色未来 今咲かん
Layering white upon white, don't let it scatter! Color upon color for the future, bloom now!
愛してバースデイ
Love me, birthday!
(Let me know)
どこで どんな景色 見てる？
Where and what scenery are you looking at?
(Let me go)
君に続け
Following right behind you
I do anything, anyway
この地図の指し示す方へ
Toward where this map points,
君の足取りたどりながら
Tracing your footsteps...
憧れを力に変えて
Turning my admiration into strength,
Rock my world, baby
あれからどれくらい君に追いつけたんだろう
How close have I gotten to catching up with you since then?
いつでも前を行くその背中を見つめ続けてきた
I've kept my eyes on your back as you always walk ahead.
遠い道のり超えて行く度に
Every time I overcome a long journey,
ホントの強さの意味を知るから...
I come to know the true meaning of strength...
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I throw everything away,
君との距離感詰め切れなくて...
I still can't seem to close the distance between us...
あの日々あの時思い出せば
When I recall those days and those moments,
この想いよ届け
Let these feelings reach you!
(Let me know)
どこでどんな景色見てる？
Where and what scenery are you looking at?
(Let me go)
君に続け
Following right behind you
I do anything, anyway
いつかは誰かが私の背中を追うようになるかも
Someday, someone might start chasing after my back too,
それでもペースは落とさずに
Even so, without slowing down my pace,
Run to you, baby
振り返らずにゴールを目指し走っていく
I run towards the goal without looking back,
いつも自分が頂の上にいることだけ信じて
Believing only that I will always be at the top!
たとえ何度も壁を感じても
Even if I feel like hitting a wall time and time again,
いばらの道を乗り越えてみせる
I will show that I can overcome this path of thorns!
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I throw everything away,
君との距離感詰め切れなくて...
I still can't seem to close the distance between us...
あの日々あの時思い出せば
When I recall those days and those moments,
この想いよ届け
Let these feelings reach you!
(Let me know)
どこでどんな景色見てる？
Where and what scenery are you looking at?
(Let me go)
君に続け
Following right behind you
I do anything, anyway
また君と会える日を信じて
Believing in the day I can meet you again,
受け止めた想いを未来へと届けるのさ
I will deliver these cherished feelings into the future!
全てを投げ出したとしてもまだ
Even if I throw everything away,
君との距離感詰め切れなくて...
I still can't seem to close the distance between us...
あの日々あの時思い出せば
When I recall those days and those moments,
この想いよ届け
Let these feelings reach you!
(Let me know)
どこでどんな景色見てる？
Where and what scenery are you looking at?
(Let me go)
君に続け
Following right behind you
I do anything, anyway
Let me know
One for the one
Ah 海岸沿いイカした奴らが集まるあのお店
Ah, that coastal shop where cool guys gather,
二人のステージ
Is a stage for the two of us!
Ah 双子みたいねばっちりまつげは今日も潮風
Ah, like twins, our perfect eyelashes are facing the sea breeze again today,
受け止めているわ
Taking it all in.
二人が踊り出したらほら
When the two of us start dancing, look,
誰にも負けないわ
We won't lose to anyone!
Let's dance tonight
海岸通りの噂 私たちのものなの
The rumors on the coastal drive belong to us.
虜にするわ 逃がさない
I'll captivate you, I won't let you get away.
Come on, come on, come on, my darling
渚に踊る 君と私は
Dancing on the beach, you and I are...
今も昔も レディーマーメイド
...Lady Mermaids, both now and in the past.
恋も束の間 夏は重大事
Love is fleeting, but summer is a big deal.
人魚な恋はね 儚いものなの
Love for a mermaid is so ephemeral.
泣いて笑ったね End of the summer
We cried and laughed, end of the summer.
One for the one
Ah 彼氏と街の景色は変わっていくさ
Ah, boyfriends and cityscapes keep changing...
二人は変わらないけど
...but the two of us will never change.
Ah コンクリートに消えてなくなる砂浜
Ah, the sandy beach disappearing under the concrete...
なんだか切なくなるね
...somehow makes me feel so bittersweet.
君が街を飛び出してさ
You ran away from this town...
夢と共に暮らした City my life, my way
...living with your dreams in the city, my life, my way.
都会の匂い憧れ 君がいなくなったの
Longing for the city scent, you were gone.
独りの海は 冷たすぎて
The sea alone was far too cold.
Get back, get back, get back, my friend
海辺の街で 二人で一つ
In the seaside town, the two of us are as one.
ずっと前から 一緒さ
We've been together for so long.
秋が来たなら 潮が引くように
When autumn arrives, like the tide receding...
彼も車も いなくなるかね
...will he and his car be gone too?
海岸通りを 飛ばそうぜ
Let me speed down the coastal drive!
渚に踊る 君と私は
Dancing on the beach, you and I are...
今も昔も レディーマーメイド
...Lady Mermaids, both now and in the past.
恋も束の間 夏は重大事
Love is fleeting, but summer is a big deal.
一夏の夢と かたづけてみても
Even if I try to write it off as a summer dream...
二人の泣いてた End of the summer
...we were both crying, end of the summer.
海辺の街で 二人で一つ
In the seaside town, the two of us are as one.
ずっと前から 一緒さ
We've been together for so long.
冬の潮風 頬を突き刺すわ
The winter sea breeze pierces our cheeks...
季節外れの レディーマーメイド
...an out-of-season Lady Mermaid.
泣いて笑ったね End of the summer
We cried and laughed, end of the summer.
海岸通りを 飛ばそうぜ
Let me speed down the coastal drive!
One for the one
We did it!
Okay! Let's start right ahead with an introduction!
Hello everybody, my name is Mint Fantome. I am a costume VTuber.
I'm not a part of Hololive, but I am a big fan of Miss Takanashi Kiara!
Is this our first ever 3D appearance together?
Together!
And we sang a beautiful song that I think means a lot to both of us!
Both of us!
What's it called? It was Lady Mermaid!
From some two beautiful ladies from Hello! Project, Suzuki Airi and Sugaya Risako...
Who by now you guys really remember those names, right?
...of the Easter Live that I had, okay?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So it's teleproject all over again.
We had a lot of fun with that, right?
We did!
Practicing together...
Oh my gosh...
...shaking the booty!
When we were doing practice, every time we would like do the...
...this part, we would stare at each other...
...like, "Look at me! Shake the booty!"
So fun, yeah!
I'm so happy that we're together!
Me too!
And you're here!
I know!
It's like...
It's like you're p- honestly, it really does feel like this is a different timeline!
Where, like, somehow you ended up here!
Yeah, maybe!
It is kind of fun to like...
Today, today I'm roleplaying!
Yeah, yeah, yeah! A little bit!
Oooh, I wonder which generation you're from if you're roleplaying.
Oooh!
And then I also got to see the big wall of the signatures and everything!
Oh, signatures!
Yeah, it's been really exciting being here at the hololive studio, so...
Thank you, everybody! Thank you, Kiara-sama!
Thank you for having me!
Yeah, it's my first time having an external guest, so that's exciting!
What? Really?
Yeah!
Woah!
Yeah, I've been like kind of trying to get something going for a while, but it never worked out...
...but now finally, you're ready!
Like, I was gonna like, honestly, invite you earlier, but...
...you know, it took you a while to...
I feel too...
I feel too honored for this!
I feel like I'm too small for this position!
No, no!
Okay!
So anyway...
This was a special time, but so...
Yes!
Uh, fact is... fact of the matter is...
You are a maid...
Yes!
...and you have to like kind of pay for this exposure I've given you.
Oh! Oh, I see.
So I would like you to clean the stage, please, 'cause there's dirt! Dirt, dirt, dirt!
Oh! Oh!
Get rid of it!
Where did this come from?
You're a maid, right? Clean it up!
I have no materials! I'll just use my hands...
Yeah!
Why is it not going away?
You're so bad at this!
I'm sorry, Ojo-sama!
Goddammit!
Ojo-sama!
Let me kiss your feet!
You better!
All the KFP are crying right now.
Get to work!
It's not going away!
Mamma mia, oh my god!
Can you not do anything right?!
I'm sorry, Ojo-sama, please forgive me! Don't kick me out!
No! I will not forgive you! I will show you how it's done!
Okay!
Yeah!
I am going to get you!
What are you doing?!
You see that? You see that? I'm gonna get you!
Turn it up to the top,
let's get it started, go non-stop!
Bust through the door, we don't knock,
just have a good time!
Like we never cared about what they say,
tear up the place like it's our own,
get wilder than a cyclone,
and leave it on a high note!
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky!
Yeah, when we're together, we don't have to try!
If you wanna join, then this is your invite!
Show 'em what you got, come on, don't be shy!
We, we are breaking through borders!
Free, like the clouds are beneath us, oh!
We, we're like diamonds in starlight!
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight!
We (we are), we're just living this moment!
Free (free, yeah), on this path that we've chosen, oh!
We (we are), we're like diamonds in starlight!
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight!
Caught inside a bubble full of doubts,
it's time to make it pop!
Baby, just believe it, feel it, lose control, it's in your blood!
You know there ain't nobo-bo-body getting down like we do!
There ain't no pa-pa-party like a party with Miku!
And it's just like magic, lighting up the sky!
Yeah, when we're together, we don't have to try!
If you wanna join, then this is your invite!
Show 'em what you got, come on, don't be shy!
We (we), we are breaking through borders!
Free (free), like the clouds are beneath us, oh!
We (we are), we're like diamonds in starlight!
We shine in the dark night 'cause we are the highlight!
We (we are), we're just living this moment!
We
On this path that we've chosen, oh
We're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night
'Cause we are the highlight
Don't lose your dream, make it reality, baby
Don't lose your dream, make it
Now everybody let me hear you say!
Don't lose your dream, go and make history, baby
Don't lose your dream
We
We are breaking through borders
Free
Like nobody can stop us, oh
We are diamonds in starlight
'Cause you know that we are
We (We are)
We are breaking through borders
Free (Free, yeah)
Like the clouds are beneath us, oh
We (We are)
We're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night
'Cause we are the highlight
We (We are)
We're just living this moment
Free (Free, yeah)
On this path that we've chosen, oh
We (We are)
We're like diamonds in starlight
We shine in the dark night
'Cause we are the highlight
Highlight, highlight, highlight!
Highlight, highlight, highlight! Yeah!
That was another banger from KIRA!
And I did it with all my beloved ID girls! I love you! I love you, ID girls!
I love you so much!
Yes! So, after this wonderful banger,
as you may have noticed, if you look at the time...
Mmm, it might be time to end soon.
And therefore, I will introduce some merchandise to you guys!
It's birthday merchandise time!
ではでは、誕生日記念のグッズ出てるので紹介したいと思います！どうぞ！
So then, birthday commemorative merch is out, so I'd like to introduce it! Here you go!
見ていきましょう！Let's check it out!
Let me show you! Let's check it out!
That is the overview,
and now let me show you all of them in detail.
First of all, the tapestry!
Tada!
As you can tell, I am in a wedding dress!
なんと！なんと！私、なんか可愛い服着てますね！あー、恥ずかしい！
Look at that! Look at that! I'm wearing such cute clothes! Ah, how embarrassing!
Yeah, um, it's about time, right? I don't know, heh.
It's a beautiful tapestry. I haven't done a tapestry in a while, so I thought you guys deserve one.
And next, with the same beautiful face,
and a different expression perhaps,
it will be a little badge.
So if you are a badge collector, now's the time!
If you have an itabag or something to fill up,
now's the time to get yourself a Wawa badge, a Wawawaifu badge!
Oh, and by the way, the illustration is by DOTORI!
Thank you so much! It's so beautiful, and looks so cute!
バッジ集めてる人もぜひ今回、どうぞいっぱい買ってください！ありがとうございます！
For those who collect badges as well, please go ahead and buy lots of them this time! Thank you very much!
And next up is the lamp!
Yeah, the title is...
'You Light Up My Life Lamp'.
You, because it's a chicken, it's a KFP chicken!
はい！私の人生を照らしてくれるのがあなたなので、その姿をしたランプでございます！
Yes! Since you are the one who lights up my life, this is a lamp in that form!
And next we have the Anger Management Frog Ball!
Froggy Wawa! Perfect, right?
You want to squeeze it, squish her head, don't you? Me too!
えー、怒って、おこ、おこマネジメント、カエルボールでございます！フロッギーワワの顔付いてるボールです。とってもキュートですけど、
Uh, the Anger Management Frog Ball! It's a ball with Froggy Wawa's face on it. It's super cute, but...
なんかね、ちょっと押したいんだよね！うん！
You know, you kinda want to press it, right? Yep!
And next, we have a situational voice!
Yes, it is matching
with the tapestry, actually.
So this, it fits it, you know, like,
on this whole like honeymoon wedding situation.
And normally I don't really go that hard on the romance in my voice packs,
so it's embarrassing, but just this time! Just this once!
だけ
Only...
えーっと、ちょっと恥ずかしい
Um, it's a bit embarrassing,
ロマンチックなシチュエーションです。
a romantic situation.
タペストリーに合わせてます。
It matches the tapestry.
日本語もあります。
There's a Japanese version too.
よかったらどうぞ！
Please check it out if you'd like!
And for the full set, if you want the full set,
you will get a postcard,
extra,
and a limited amount will be signed by me with my hand,
and the rest will be stamped.
数量限定は私のサインが入る
The limited edition has my handwritten signature
ポストカードが特典になっています。
on the postcard as a bonus.
で、そのほかはスタンプです。
And the rest will have a foil stamp.
And another special bonus if you get the full set...
is a Hololive Card! Special Hololive Card, yeah!
This can be used in the Hololive Official Card Game,
but you have to purchase the full set through the official website,
GeekJack or any others are not possible.
If you want to learn how to play, please check out the Hololive Official Card Game website, yeah!
タレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典として
As a full-set bonus for talent premium merch,
もう1つ追加でこのカードが付いてきます！
one additional card comes with it!
はい、ちゃんとHololive Official Card Gameで使用できます！
Yes, it can properly be used in the Hololive Official Card Game!
やったー！
Yay!
えーっと、カードの詳細につきましては
Um, for details on the card,
Hololive Official Card Gameの公式ホームページにてご確認ください。
please check the official Hololive Official Card Game website.
イェーイ！イェーイ！ナイス！特典が2つ！
Yay! Yay! Nice! Two bonuses!
And next, after all this merch announcement,
let me just tell you that the merch will be, you know, you can get it
after the next song,
because the next song
will be my next original song!
And it's called "TASTY"!
じゃじゃーん！
Tada!
Yes! "TASTY" is the name of my next original song,
and it will start being released on all streaming services
at midnight your time, whatever your time zone is, it will be up at midnight.
But the music video will come up right after this,
we will raid into it, unless it doesn't work,
but we will raid into it, and you will see the music video.
And after the music video, the merch will be available
at the 10-minute mark of whatever hour you are in. Okay?
私の新曲です！
It's my new song!
やったー！
Yay!
『TASTY』でございます！
It's called "TASTY"!
この後配信もしますし、この後MVも公開されます！
It will be available for streaming after this, and the MV will be released right after!
で、その後にグッズも出ます！
And merch will go on sale after that!
よろしくお願いします！
Please check it out!
イェーイ！
Yay!
So with that, it is finally time
for the last song of my birthday live,
and my new original song.
So please listen to "TASTY".
Tongue tied, oh you don't gotta hide it
Obvious I get you excited
Don't want perfume on my skin, just need you, yeah
Sugary thoughts, nah I don't mind it
Confection affection, it feels right
Flavor makes you go
No beggin' needed, just take a bite
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive
Feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see
What we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive, so sweet
You got me like that
That that that
T-taste me
Gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me
Tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
Baby look at my picture
Know you wanna be my mister, mister
I can be a little bitter, switch up, whimper, worship me like I'm scripture
This sickly sweet
Candied love
Makes you want more, mm wow
Are you satisfied now?
Hear you say
You want me
Can't stop the way your eyes wander, oh
So dolce
Lemme show you what I can take, make ache
I'll make you feel like you're alive
Alive
Feel your heartbeat
Honey drippin', you see
What we've done tonight
Just a little taste of me
Sweet like sugar, rotten down to the core
Savor every little taste, give you more
Flavored hard candy, addictive, so sweet
You got me like that
That that that that
Ooh
Sweet aroma
Got us both actin' up tonight
Ooh
Sugar coma
Fall into me you want it
Baby, I'm sweet for you
I'ma keep it tasty, tasty
Know you like this taste, taste, taste
T-taste me
Gettin' every drop
You know you like it a lot
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
Taste me
Tell me what do you want
I'll be your la-lollipop
You know I'm taste-taste-taste-tasty
So sweet, not enough of me
Drippin' sugary, just for you
So sweet, got a crush on me
Sugar rush right into you
Not enough of me Drippin -
So sweet, got a crush on me Sugar rush